A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 17727-19980 FA739G
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 17727-19980
1936-2005
1950s-1990s
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA739G
5.39 Cubic Feet 17 containers total including but not limited to Document boxes 886-898.
Conditions Governing Access
Catalogued Reports are open for research with select reports restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
The Catalogued Reports are arranged numerically by an arbitrary call number assigned during cataloging, from 1 to approximately 20,000.
Scope and Contents
The Ford Foundation's Catalogued Reports collection includes policy and programming documents, program evaluations, and periodic program status reports produced by Foundation officers and staff, as well as consultants and grantees. Some published material produced by Ford Foundation grants is also included in the collection. The collection also includes some of the Ford Foundation's own publications, such as the Annual Reports and newsletters.
- Terminal report from Banaras (mimeo) (Reports 017727) (EL 68-4), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EL 68-4)
  Program Name
  Overseas Division/South and Southeast Asia; International Division/South and Southeast Asia/International Division/Asia and the Pacific
  Ford Foundation Series
  India Reports; Education-Law
  Law schools -- India; Law -- Study and teaching -- India
- Draft observations on legal education in India (mimeo) (Reports 017728) (EL 71-1), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EL 71-1)
- Urban community organisation and communal harmony (mimeo) (Reports 017729) (EL 71-2), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EL 71-2)
- Reflections on India trip (mimeo) (Reports 017730) (CD 55-1), 1955 (Box 935, Sheet CD 55-1)
  Overseas Division/South and Southeast Asia; International Division/South and Southeast Asia; International Division/Asia and the Pacific
  India Reports; Community Development
  Rural development -- India; Community development -- India
- Educational approach in community development (mimeo) (Reports 017731) (CD 58-5), 1958 (Box 935, Sheet CD 58-5)
- Elements of program planning in villages and blocks (mimeo) (Reports 017732) (CD 58-6), 1958 (Box 935, Sheet CD 58-6)
- Some principles related to the role of extension education in community development (mimeo) (Reports 017733) (CD 59-5), 1959 (Box 935, Sheet CD 59-5)
  Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Rural extension -- India; Education, Rural -- India
- Study of local bodies inside and at the periphery of Delhi State (mimeo) (Reports 017734) (CD 59-7), 1959 (Box 935, Sheet CD 59-7)
- Central Institute of Study and Research in community development - a sociological study of Panchayati Raj in Rajasthan and Andhra Pradesh - (mimeo) (Reports 017735) (CD 61-3), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet CD 61-3)
- Panchayati Raj in Andhra Pradesh - some observations and some unanswered questions (mimeo) (Reports 017736) (CD 61-4), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet CD 61-4)
- Evaluation study of the formation and working of Vikas Mandals (mimeo) (Reports 017737) (CD 61-6), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet CD 61-6a, CD61-6b)
- Teaching, research and extension in rural social sciences (mimeo) (Reports 017738) (CD 62-5), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet CD 62-5)
- On the application of propaganda principles to the community development programme (mimeo) (Reports 017739), 1963 (Box 886, Box 935, Sheet CD 63-3)
- The village level worker service: the institution and its impact (mimeo) (Reports 017740) (CD 64-3), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet CD 64-3)
- Faith in the people (mimeo) (Reports 017741) (CD 64-5), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet CD 64-5)
- The touch of freedom in new hands - for Indian Institute of opinion research (mimeo) (Reports 017742) (CD 64-6), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet CD 64-6)
- Rural development category I - training women for village extension work in home economics (mimeo) (Reports 017743) (CD 64-7), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet CD 64-7)
- Rural Development Category I - Report No. Two: Rural Village Development and Extension Training Centres (mimeo) (Reports 017744) (CD 65-1), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-1)
- Rural development category I - report no. four: village artisan workshop wings (mimeo) (Reports 017745) (CD 65-2), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-2)
- Rural development category I - report no. five: social education organizer training centres (mimeo) (Reports 017746) (CD 65-3), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-3)
  Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Education, Rural -- India
- Rural development category I - report no. seven: block development officer training centers (mimeo) (Reports 017747) (CD 65-3), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-4)
- Rural development category I - report no. six: National Institute of Community Development (mimeo) (Reports 017748) (CD 65-5), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-5)
- The village level worker (VLW): some suggestions for making him a more effective community development and agricultural worker (mimeo) (Reports 017749) (CD 65-6), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet CD 65-6)
- Village level worker - incentive action and evaluation program (mimeo) (Reports 017750) (CD 66-1), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet CD 66-1)
- Study at the University of Pittsburg, USA (mimeo) (Reports 017751) (CD 67-1), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet CD 67-1)
- Program evaluation in India (Reports 017752) (CD 67-4), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet CD 67-4)
- A briefing paper on the objectives, organization and work of the the Central Small Industries Organization and The Small Industries Service Institutes in relation the Small Industries Programme and industrial development in India (mimeo) (Reports 017753) (EA 62-2), 1962 (Box 936, Sheet EA 62-2)
  India Reports; Economics & Administration
  Economic development projects -- India; Small business -- India
- The sociologist and social change in underdeveloped countries (mimeo) (Reports 017754), 1962
  Economic development projects -- India; Political science -- India
- The provision of special training for leaders and key personnel responsible for the general development of the Panchayati Raj System (mimeo) (Reports 017755) (EA 62-14), 1962 (Box 936, Sheet EA 62-14)
  Economic development projects -- India; Management -- India
- A memorandum on the need for courses in the United Kingdom to aid the development of local government overseas and the methods by which these can be provided (mimeo) (Reports 017756) (EA 62-16), 1962 (Box 936, Sheet EA 62-16)
  Economic development projects -- India; Management -- India; Political science -- Study and teaching -- India
- Issues involved in economic and defence co-ordination in India (mimeo) (Reports 017757) (EA 63-4), 1963 (Box 936, Sheet EA 63-4)
  Abstract/Summary
  Sent to T. T. Krishnamachari
  Economic development projects -- India; Management -- India; Political science -- India
- Action program for Calcutta area (mimeo) (Reports 017758) (EA 64-8), 1964 (Box 936, Sheet EA 64-8)
  Economic development projects -- India; Management -- India; Economic development -- India
- Address to the World Traffic Engineering Conference Washington DC (Reports 017759), undated
- Educational planning and economic criteria in India's context (mimeo) (Reports 017760) (EA 66-1), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-1)
  Economic development projects -- India; Education -- India; Economic development -- India
- Housing in India for lowest income groups (mimeo) (Reports 017761) (EA 66-5), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-5)
  Housing -- India; City planning -- India; Urban development -- India
- IBM 1620 computer installations for New Delhi area - related problems and needs for immediate attention (mimeo) (Reports 017762) (EA 66-9), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-9)
  Economic development projects -- India; Economic development -- India
- Innovation in administration and economic development (Reports 017763) (EA 66-10), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-10)
- Center-state relations - preliminary statement (mimeo) (Reports 017764) (EA 66-17), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-17)
  Related Materials
  See also: "Politics, Parliament and the Constitution of India", background paper, November 1966. EA 66-21, box 936.
- An environmental approach to low-income housing (mimeo) (Reports 017765) (EA 66-18), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-18)
  Housing -- India; City planning -- India
- Planning "Yes", Zoning "No" (mimeo) (Reports 017766) (EA 66-20), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-20)
  City planning -- India; Housing -- India
- Training in state administration (mimeo) (Reports 017767) (EA 66-22), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-22)
  Education -- India; Political science -- Study and teaching -- India
- Study of commercial establishments in Asansol and Durgapur (with a special emphasis on the implication of present commercial structure on the proposed Durgapur City Centre)...transmittal (mimeo) (Reports 017768) (EA 66-25), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-25)
  Memorandum from B. K. Lee to Sivaramakrishnan, Row, Kingsley et. al.
- Personal to Ensminger, William Douglas from dad (mimeo) (Reports 017769) (EA 66-26), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EA 66-26)
- Applications of urban community development in the Calcutta Metropolitan Plan (mimeo) (Reports 017770) (EA 67-3), 1967 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet EA 67-3)
  City planning -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Small business -- India
- Background information on new center and state governments (mimeo) (Reports 017771) (EA 67-4), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-4)
  City planning -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Political science -- India
- The annual assessment and production system in Indian bureaucracy (mimeo) (Reports 017772) (EA 67-6), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-6)
  Political science -- India
- Planning (T and CP) department sic government of West Bengal (Reports 017773), 1967
  Economic development projects -- India; Political science -- India; City planning -- India
- Motivating hospital employees (mimeo) (Reports 017774) (EA 67-9), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-9)
  Management -- India; Education -- India; Economic development projects -- India
- Hospital administration volume IV, No 2 (Reports 017775), 1967
- Time and the nature of infant industry economies (mimeo) (Reports 017776) (EA 67-10), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-10)
  Management -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Small business -- India
- Foundation assistance to Nepal termination report (mimeo) (Reports 017777) (EA 67-11), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-11)
  Economic development projects -- Nepal
- Scope of planning (letters and notes on water resources planning and organization as might apply in India (mimeo) (Reports 017778) (EA 67-12), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-12)
- Consultancy on science policy and organization with the Indian Institute of Public Administration (mimeo) (Reports 017779) (EA 67-13), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-13)
  City planning -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Indian Institute of Public Administration
- Center-state relations and the center's food policies (mimeo) (Reports 017780) (EA 67-15), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-15)
- End of Tour Report - East India Regional Planning Project (mimeo) (Reports 017781) (EA 67-16), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-16)
  Economic development projects -- India
- Center-state relations: West Bengal and the problems of law and order (mimeo) (Reports 017782) (EA 67-17), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-17)
- Report and recommendations on India - Institute of Public Administration Program (mimeo) (Reports 017783) (EA 67-20), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-20)
  Economic development projects -- India; Institute of Public Administration Program
- End of assignment observations on I.A.P.A. (Institute of Public Administration Program) (mimeo) (Reports 017784) (EA 67-21), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-21)
- A summary of development data - Assam state 1967 (mimeo) (Reports 017785) (EA 67-23) (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-23)
- Status report on the Calcutta Metropolitan Plan Project (mimeo) (Reports 017786) (EA 67-25), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-25)
  Economic development projects -- India; Calcutta Metropolitan Plan Project
- The Indian Institute of Public Administration - policies for government pay (mimeo) (Reports 017787) (EA 67-26), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-26)
  Economic development projects -- India; Indian Institute of Public Administration
- Memorandum report on termination of my long-term assignment as an advisor to the Calcutta Metropolitan Planning Organisation (mimeo) (Reports 017788) (EA 67-28), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-28)
  City planning -- India; Calcutta Metropolitan Planning Organisation
- End of tour report (Public administration) (mimeo) (Reports 017789) (EA 67-29), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-29)
- End of tour report (Bhubaneswar) (mimeo) (Reports 017790) (EA 67-30), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-30)
- Some administrative short-comings of intensive agricultural development efforts (mimeo) (Reports 017791) (EA 67-31), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-31)
- Analysis and projection or urban population Bihar (mimeo) (Reports 017792) (EA 67-36), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-36)
  City planning -- India; Economic development projects -- India
- The Indian Institute of Public Administration - administration of a pay system (mimeo) (Reports 017793) (EA 67-38), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-38)
  The Indian Institute of Public Administration -- India; Economic development projects -- India
- The role of the Ford Foundation in urban development planning in India (mimeo) (Reports 017794) (EA 67-39), 1967 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet EA 67-39)
- Final report on the regional planning project for Eastern India (mimeo) (Reports 017795) (EA 67-39a), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-39a)
- Proposed Foundation strategy on administrative reforms (mimeo) (Reports 017796) (EA 67-40), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-40)
  Management -- India; Economic development projects -- India
- Economic planning (mimeo) (Reports 017797) (EA 67-41), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-41)
- Toward a program of assisting in development of India's political leadership (mimeo) (Reports 017798) (EA 67-42), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-42)
  Politics and government -- India; Economic development projects -- India
- The political situation (mimeo) (Reports 017799) (EA 67-43), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-43)
- Discussion paper 'Urban studies and developing countries' forwarded by Jack Bresnan (mimeo) (Reports 017800) (EA 67-46), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-46)
  City planning -- India
- Planning and project evaluation (mimeo) (Reports 017801) (EA 67-47), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EA 67-47)
- Report on the Foundation's activities in the field of economic planning and training in Nepal -- 1954-1968 (mimeo) (Reports 017802) (EA 68-1) (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-1)
- Report on consultantship - the Indian Institute of Public Administration, New Delhi (mimeo) (Reports 017803) (EA 68-2), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-2)
- Foundation strategy and responsibilities in improving economic policy - end of assignment report (mimeo) (Reports 017804) (EA 68-3a), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-3a)
- End of assignment report / John Taylor (mimeo) (Reports 017805) (EA 68-5), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-5)
- End of assignment report: afterthoughts of my five year with the Calmetro project in Calcutta (mimeo) (Reports 017806) (EA 68-6), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-6)
- Performance Budget... (mimeo) (Reports 017807) (EA 68-6a), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 68-6a)
- A proposal for regional planning in Nepal (mimeo) (Reports 017808) (EA 68-9), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EA 61-5, Sheet EA 68-9)
- Suggested curriculum for the Center for Economic Development and Administration (mimeo) (Reports 017809) (EA 69-1), 1969 (Box 936, Sheet EA 69-1)
- A report on the progress of planning for an all-India science talent search (mimeo) (Reports 017810) (EdR 59-1), 1959 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 59-1)
  India Reports; Education and Research
  Education -- India
- Education for social usefulness (Reports 017811) (EdR 69-1), 1963 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 69-1)
- Baroda College of Home Science (Reports 017812) (EdR 69-2), 1959 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 69-2)
  Education -- India; Education (Higher) -- India
- Some Observations on the Banaras Law Department (Reports 017813) (EdR 69-3), 1969 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 69-3)
  Education -- India; Law -- Study and teaching -- India
- The Delhi University university computer center (Reports 017814) (EdR 69-8), 1969 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 69-8)
- Indian education in the seventies (section I and II) (Reports 017815) (EdR 70-3), 1970 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 70-3)
- National service by students in urban slums (Reports 017816) (EdR 70-6a), 1970 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 70-6a)
  Education -- India; Education (Higher) -- India; Rural education -- India
- Role of students in promoting community development in urban slums (Reports 017817) (EdR 70-6b), 1970 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 70-6b)
- For education and related activities in population and management (Reports 017818) (EdR 70-25), 1970 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 70-25)
- The role of utilization research on SITE (Reports 017819) (EdR 70-26), 1970 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 70-26)
  Education -- India; Education (Higher) -- India; Education -- Research -- India
- Linkage with industry: a key problem for technician training institutions, Febrary (Reports 017820) (EdR 71-4), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 71-4)
  Education -- India; Education (Higher) -- India; Technical education -- India; Vocational education -- India
- A note on adult education in India (Reports 017821) (EdR 71-5), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 71-5)
  Education -- India; Adult education
- Education and employment - some fundamental rethinking and new approaches proposed in Ceylon (Reports 017822) (EdR 71-11), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 71-11)
  Education -- India; Employment -- India
- Summary of remarks (Reports 017823) (EdR 72-4), 1972 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 72-4)
- A tentative plan for evaluation of the work experience program in 570 schools in Maharashtra (Reports 017824) (EdR 72-6), 1972 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 72-6)
  Education -- India; Schools -- Evaluation -- India
- Evaluation research project in occupational education and training, Maharashtra 1972-73 (Reports 017825) (EdR 72-9) (Box 936, Sheet EdR 72-9)
- Work oriented general education (Reports 017826) (EdR 72-7), 1972 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 72-7)
  Preliminary draft for comments and discussion
  Education -- India; Vocational education -- India
- Developing a tool for development: television in India (an overview of current situation) (Reports 017827) (EdR 72-13), 1971 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 72-13)
- How can education and training be made more effective in India's struggle against poverty (Reports 017828) (EdR 73-2), 1973 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 73-2)
  Education -- India; Education -- Study and teaching -- India
- Education and planning and human resources development in fourth plan (Reports 017829) (EdR 74-3), 1974 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 74-3)
  Education -- India; Education -- Study and teaching -- India; Education -- Planning -- India
- A school community in relation to rural development: Sri Ramakrishna Mission Vidyalaya - Coimbatore (Reports 017830) (EdR 74-5), 1974 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 74-5)
  Education -- India; Rural education -- India
- Five year plan for a rural school (Reports 017831) (EdR 74-6), 1974 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 74-6)
  Education -- India; Rural education -- India; Rural schools -- India
- Rural development through non-formal education - suggested research strategy (Reports 017832) (EdR 74-8), 1974 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 74-8)
- Memorandum on possible additional support to the rural institutes (Reports 017833) (EdR 74-9), 1974 (Box 936, Sheet EdR 74-9)
- Evaluation of educational programs (mimeo) (Reports 017834) (ED 59-4), 1959 (Box 936, Sheet ED 59-4)
  India Reports; Education
  Education -- Evaluation -- India
- A report on home science (mimeo) (Reports 017835) (ED 60-3), 1960 (Box 936, Sheet ED 60-3)
  Education -- Science -- India
- A report on architectural education in India (mimeo) (Reports 017836) (ED 60-4), 1960 (Box 936, Sheet ED 60-4)
  Education, Higher -- India
- Survey of special problems and needs of the University of Calcutta (mimeo) (Reports 017837) (ED 61-3), 1962 (Box 936, Sheet ED 61-3)
  Education, Higher -- India; University of Calcutta
- Proposal for the establishment of the Delhi National University (mimeo) (Reports 017838) (ED 61-4), 1961 (Box 936, Sheet ED 61-4)
  Education, Higher -- India; Delhi National University
- Educational planning and specifications for the building of the National Institute of Education (mimeo) (Reports 017839) (ED 61-6), 1961 (Box 936, Sheet ED 61-6)
  Education, Higher -- India; National Institute of Education
- Educational television project, Delhi higher secondary schools (mimeo) (Reports 017840) (ED 61-8), 1961 (Box 936, Sheet ED 61-8)
  Education, Higher -- India; Education, Secondary -- India
- Indian libraries and the India Wheat Loan Educational Exchange program - a report (mimeo) (Reports 017841) (ED 61-10), 1961 (Box 936, Sheet ED 61-10)
  Education -- India; Libraries -- India
- Report and observations - TV project visitation (mimeo) (Reports 017842) (ED 63-5), 1963 (Box 936, Sheet ED 63-5)
- Woodstock school - report of survey (mimeo) (Reports 017843) (ED 63-8), 1963 (Box 936, Sheet ED 63-8)
  Education -- India; Education, Secondary -- India
- Applied linguistics in India (mimeo) (Reports 017844) (ED 64-7), 1964 (Box 936, Sheet ED 64-7)
  Education -- India; Language and education -- India
- Delhi school TV project (mimeo) (Reports 017845) (ED 64-8), 1964 (Box 936, Sheet ED 64-8)
- Prospectus for a new National Institution of Higher Learning In India (mimeo), August 1964 / (Reports 017846) (ED 64-9) (Box 936, Sheet ED 64-9)
  Education -- India; Education, Higher -- India
- The University of Delhi - Ten year development plan (mimeo) (Reports 017847) (ED 65-1), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-1)
  Education -- India; Education, Higher -- India; The University of Delhi
- Delhi School TV project - consultants report on visitation (mimeo) (Reports 017848) (ED 65-5), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-5)
- Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani (mimeo) (Reports 017849) (ED 65-6), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-6)
  Education -- India; Education, Higher -- India; Birla Institute of Technology and Science (BITS)
- Comparative analysis, model act report (1964) and Calcutta University Bill (mimeo) (Reports 017850) (ED 65-7), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-7)
- Summary report on my visit to Bits (mimeo) (Reports 017851) (ED 65-8), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-8)
- General education - a lever for raising the level of college education (mimeo) (Reports 017852), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet ED 65-9)
- Educational television in India (mimeo) (Reports 017853) (ED 65-14), 1965; Microfiche, 8 sheets. (Box 936, Sheet ED 65-14)
  Education -- India; Educational broadcasting -- India
- Educational television in India - a perspective (mimeo) (Reports 017854) (ED 66-1), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-1)
- Report on the chemical engineering department at BITs (mimeo) (Reports 017855) (ED 66-2), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-2)
- The strengthening of University of Delhi (mimeo) (Reports 017856) (ED 66-12), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-12)
  Education -- India; Education, Higher -- India; University of Delhi
- A report on the department of Chinese studies at Delhi University (mimeo) (Reports 017857) (ED 66-15), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-15)
  Education -- India; Language and education; Education, Higher -- India; University of Delhi
- Project report on an educational institution in the name of Jawaharlal Nehru (mimeo) (Reports 017858) (ED 66-16), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-16)
- Report on general education and the Kennedy Centre, Aligarh Muslim University (mimeo) (Reports 017859) (ED 66-17), 1966 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet ED 66-17)
- Better rural education for a true India (mimeo) (Reports 017860) (ED 66-22), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet ED 66-22)
- Report on visit to BITS (mimeo) (Reports 017861) (ED 67-1), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet ED 67-1)